<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Return Rambling</title>
    <description></description>
    <link>http://Smittey.co.uk</link>
    <atom:link href="http://Smittey.co.uk/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
		<author>Andy Smith</author>
        <title>Git Privacy</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I am an avid &lt;a href=&quot;http://smittey.co.uk/datarize-my-life/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;data nut and life-tracker&lt;/a&gt;. Anybody who knows me and has spent time with me will have seen me track the types of beer that I’m drinking, analyze my sleeping habits, and much more. I do this for me, and often to crunch numbers. I have weird hobbies, what can I say. Despite appearing that I happily give apps and services my personal information, I do think carefully about who I trust having my private (and valuable) data. Second to this, I am very cautious about who has access to my contact information, namely phone number and email address. I received an email recently which got me slightly worried… It was an email from a company who wanted me to work for them (a blanket email no doubt). Why was this weird? It was delivered to my work email address.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://Smittey.co.uk/git-privacy/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://Smittey.co.uk/git-privacy/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
		<author>Andy Smith</author>
        <title>Top 10 Developer Podcasts</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I spend a lot of time in my car. Like, a crazy amount of time. It’s normally my preferred method of transport as it gives me the freedom to go where I want and when I want without enduring the unreliable nature of the public transport system (which if you’re following the UK Southern Train News right now then you will know just how bad it is). I even prefer driving the lengthy 350 miles back to my home town over a shorter train ride (quiet, Americans; this is a long distance for us!).&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://Smittey.co.uk/top-10-developer-podcasts/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://Smittey.co.uk/top-10-developer-podcasts/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
		<author>Andy Smith</author>
        <title>The Insecurities of a Full-Stack Developer</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I’ve been a full-stack developer for the past 2 years, of which I was the only full-stack developer on my previous project. I feel that it suits me. I don’t like staring at the same thing for too long and it scratches that itch that I have; the need to know how something works from back-to-front. I hate having knowledge gaps in the applications that I work on. “Magic happens” - my code - “magic happens” just doesn’t do it for me. I just need to know how it works and try to have some active involvement.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2016 01:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://Smittey.co.uk/the-insecurities-of-a-full-stack-developer/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://Smittey.co.uk/the-insecurities-of-a-full-stack-developer/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
		<author>Andy Smith</author>
        <title>Do you need a new job?</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Nobody should get too comfortable in their job, especially in the tech industry. Getting too comfortable normally means a decrease in learning. The learning curve has started to level off and you’ve become content. This may suit your situation, but it shouldn’t.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2016 15:10:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://Smittey.co.uk/do-you-need-a-new-job/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://Smittey.co.uk/do-you-need-a-new-job/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
		<author>Andy Smith</author>
        <title>Using Meteor Offline</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Most modern web frameworks use package managers. It’s almost unavoidable when building larger projects or projects that use modern concepts or components. They allow for easier development where dependency trees are managed along with versions and updates. Unless of course you’re working offline. Then they’re a pain in the arse.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2016 22:40:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://Smittey.co.uk/using-meteor-offline/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://Smittey.co.uk/using-meteor-offline/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
		<author>Andy Smith</author>
        <title>Backend vs Frontend Learning Curves</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I’m a backend software developer by education and trade. Sure, I &lt;a href=&quot;http://andysmith.me/#experience&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;dabble in full-stack&lt;/a&gt; and have cobbled together a few &lt;a href=&quot;http://andysmith.me/#projects&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;frontend projects&lt;/a&gt; in a hobbyist sort of way, but the main chunk of my knowledge and experience lies in (but is not limited to) Java and C technologies.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2016 23:10:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://Smittey.co.uk/backend-vs-frontend-learning-curves/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://Smittey.co.uk/backend-vs-frontend-learning-curves/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
		<author>Andy Smith</author>
        <title>Silicon Milkroundabout 11 Round-up</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Tech moves fast. No duh, right?&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2016 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://Smittey.co.uk/silicon-milkroundabout-11-round-up/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://Smittey.co.uk/silicon-milkroundabout-11-round-up/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
		<author>Andy Smith</author>
        <title>Anybody On?</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Ever been curious if anybody is currently looking at your website, watching your YouTube video, or on using your mobile app RIGHT NOW, but can’t be bothered to open up and sign into Google Analytics?&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2016 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://Smittey.co.uk/anybody-on/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://Smittey.co.uk/anybody-on/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
		<author>Andy Smith</author>
        <title>Datarize My Life</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Hi, my name’s Andy and I’m a dataholic.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2016 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://Smittey.co.uk/datarize-my-life/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://Smittey.co.uk/datarize-my-life/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
		<author>Andy Smith</author>
        <title>Raspberry Pi and the Impulse Buy</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;When I moved out of my family home I wasn’t quite aware of the challenge at hand. I owned a lot of stuff. Like, more than I thought I did. Arguably more than a lot of my friends did. I’m not saying this in a pissing-contest kind of way, no. More of a “with this kind of behaviour I’m going to end up on a channel 4 documentary”, sort of way.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://Smittey.co.uk/raspberry-pi-and-the-impulse-buy/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://Smittey.co.uk/raspberry-pi-and-the-impulse-buy/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
		<author>Andy Smith</author>
        <title>If you know me, don&#39;t read this</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I apologise for the clickbait-sounding title, but I guess in an intensely annoying way I’m just going to blend in with the rest of the Internet - which I hate. Not because I want to be different, but because I bloody hate clickbait. Perhaps I’m on the Internet far too much to not recognise when &lt;a href=&quot;javascript:void(0);&quot; data-toggle=&quot;popover&quot; data-placement=&quot;top&quot; data-trigger=&quot;focus&quot; data-content=&quot;Good lord, stop clicking these links!&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;“21 unusual uses of cheese - you wouldn’t believe #20”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; will be a pile of garbage. I’m looking at you, Buzzfeed.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://Smittey.co.uk/if-you-know-me-dont-read-this/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://Smittey.co.uk/if-you-know-me-dont-read-this/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
		<author>Andy Smith</author>
        <title>Keeping Fit as a Programmer</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Three years ago I was the fittest and strongest I have ever been. I was on my placement year during University, lived five minutes from where I worked, and was going to the gym four-five times per week. My diet was incredibly strict and aside from the fact that I drank more alcohol than during this working year than the University years combined, my lifestyle couldn’t have been better.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once the year was finished, I returned to University to complete my degree in Computer Science and continued to frequent the gym, albeit not as much, and drink far less. Which to me seemed a bit backwards, but on with the story. Despite spending on the up of 10 hours per day sitting at a computer of some description I wasn’t suffering from any discomfort such as back pain; something that course-mates and old workmates regularly complained about. I always put this down to the fact that I had a very strong core as a result of doing (by this point) two solid years of weight training at the gym. Since then I’ve returned to the same company as a full Graduate and onto a different project situated in a different office more than an hours drive away. This has meant that the time I’ve been able to dedicate to personal fitness tanked spectacularly and caused me to massively fall out of routine. Within the last six months the amount of discomfort I’ve suffered (particularly in my back) has went from exactly zero to at least a once per week affair.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://Smittey.co.uk/keeping-fit-as-a-programmer/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://Smittey.co.uk/keeping-fit-as-a-programmer/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
		<author>Andy Smith</author>
        <title>Your search returned no matches.</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I’m lucky enough to work with a lot of talented developers with a wealth of experience and many years under their belts. Most of these guys have been programming since long before I was even born and joke about Visual Basic and Fortran 90 being cutting edge when I was just learning how to talk.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://Smittey.co.uk/your-search-returned-no-matches/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://Smittey.co.uk/your-search-returned-no-matches/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
		<author>Andy Smith</author>
        <title>Learning to be Creative</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I’ve been doing creative things all of my life from playing the piano from an early age, to sketching and digital art, bouts of photography, creative writing and poetry, composing pieces of music, and web development to name a few. The truth is that I’m not a very creative person. That was slightly contradictory, I’ll rephrase… I’m not a naturally creative person; I just want to be creative.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://Smittey.co.uk/learning-to-be-creative/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://Smittey.co.uk/learning-to-be-creative/</guid>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>